stoxpoker.com 2014-04-06

# CardRunners - Privacy Policy

**CARDRUNNERS PRIVACY POLICY**

The CardRunners Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect at CardRunners web sites, how we may use that information, and with whom we may share it.

**Personal Information We Collect**

We may request that you provide certain personal information if you contact us, subscribe to our services, request technical support, provide us feedback on a particular offer or product, participate in a promotion, or seek business development/career opportunities.  The information we collect is generally limited to your full name and e-mail address, although we may request other information such as your billing address and credit card information in the event that you decide to make a transaction.  In general, we limit the amount of personal information we require to consummate a specific transaction.  For example, we will not ask for billing information unless it is necessary in connection with a billing transaction.  

If you submit an order at our website, you will be asked for information necessary to complete the transaction – such as your name, address, and credit card number, and to allow you to purchase and download products, obtain access to service and technical support, or otherwise utilize products or services that you have selected, as well as technical data concerning your computer or traffic data incidental to your Internet connection.  

The processing and transfer of the data are limited to the following purposes: fulfillment of your order(s)/subscription(s), extension/delivering product updates/service-subscriptions or licenses, service registration and activation, customer and technical support as you may request from time to time, processing renewals as you may request from time to time and internal (compliance) audits and fraud prevention. You make the decision whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the transaction or functionality on the site if the information is essential to complete the transaction or functionality.

**Non-Personal Information We Collect**

We collect certain aggregate and non-personal information when users visit our web sites. Aggregate and non-personal information does not relate to a single, identifiable visitor. It tells us information such as how many users visited our sites and the pages accessed. By collecting this information, we learn how to best tailor our web sites to our visitors. Through various tracking methods and using log files, we may track domain names, IP addresses, and browser types from people who visit our site. We use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns. Such information is not correlated with any personal information.

**Cookies**

CardRunners may use cookies from time to time. A cookie is a unique text file that a web site can send to your browser software. Cookies enable a web site to tailor information presented to you based on your browsing preferences. We may use cookies to personalize web pages during your visit to our web sites, and/or to remember you for easy navigation and access during your return visits after registering for our products, services and other offers including but not limited to documents, webcasts, events, evaluation software, e-books, etc. For these purposes, some cookies may be tied to your e-mail address.

CardRunners may also use cookies to track your visit to our web sites in order to collect aggregate data. However, this information will only be used for analytical purposes and will be limited to the minimum necessary to perform the analysis. If you do not want CardRunners to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a web site tries to put a cookie in your browser software. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use of some of the products and/or services at our website(s).

**Sharing Your Information**

From time to time, and in jurisdictions where it is permitted, we may provide your information to authorized vendors of CardRunners to communicate to you information or offers about products or services that they believe are important to you. If you prefer that we not provide your information to our business partners, you may let us know using one of the methods described in this policy. CardRunners provides a number of ways for you to ‘opt-out’ of receiving additional information from us or having us provide your personal information to our partners by ‘opt-out’ options provided at the point of collection, through e-mail notices, or through other preference management that may be available depending on the service or website. If you do not wish to continue receiving our email newsletters or bulletins you can opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to the "unsubscribe" address at the footer of the email.  In jurisdictions where sharing personal information is prohibited without your ‘opt-in’, no information will be shared without your prior consent.

**Legal Disclosures**

Please be advised that in certain instances, it may be necessary for CardRunners to disclose your personal information to government officials or otherwise as required by applicable law. No personally identifiable information will be disclosed to any law enforcement agency or governmental agency except in response to:

  * A subpoena, warrant or other process issued by a court of competent jurisdiction;

  * A legal process having the same consequence as a court-issued request for information, in that CardRunners would be in breach of local law were it to refuse to provide such information, and it or its officers, executive or employees would be subject to liability for failing to honor such legal process, provided there is a legal basis to do so; or,

  * Where such disclosure is necessary for CardRunners to enforce its legal rights pursuant to the laws of the jurisdiction from which such information was gathered, and there is a legal basis to do so.

**Security of Personal Information**

We have taken appropriate security measures, consistent with modern information practices, to protect your personal information. These measures include, on our web sites and Internet-enabled technologies, administrative, technical, physical and procedural steps to protect your data from misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, loss, alteration, or destruction.

**Managing Your Privacy Preferences**

You can manage your privacy preferences or receive answers to any questions about our privacy policy by using the "Contact Us" link at www.cardrunners.com or by sending written correspondence to 1165 N. Clark, Suite 614, Chicago, Illinois 60610 United States of America.

Published: May 1, 2010
